<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google Slides Knowledge  - RSS</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Get higher access to advanced AI in Google Workspace</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is significantly expanding access to its AI-powered features, including the Gemini model, across its suite of productivity applications. This initiative aims to bring enhanced capabilities, such as automated content generation in Google Docs, data analysis in Google Sheets, and presentation creation in Google Slides, to a broader range of users and regions globally. The expansion underscores Google&apos;s commitment to integrating advanced artificial intelligence directly into daily workflows to boost productivity and foster creativity for its users.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/google-workspace-ai-expanded-access.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/google-workspace-ai-expanded-access.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Expanding access to select Google Vids features for all users</title>
        <description>Google Vids, the AI-powered video creation app within Google Workspace, is expanding access to more Workspace customers, including those on Business Standard and Plus, Enterprise Starter, Standard, Plus, and Education Plus tiers. This tool utilizes generative AI to assist with scriptwriting, storyboarding, and raw cut generation, streamlining the creation of business videos for various purposes. It integrates seamlessly with existing Workspace applications like Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides, enhancing collaboration and content management.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/expanding-access-to-select-google-vids.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/expanding-access-to-select-google-vids.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Select Gemini in Workspace capabilities now available to Education Plus and Teaching &amp; Learning customers</title>
        <description>Google is bringing Gemini to Google Workspace for Education, offering AI-powered assistance for educators to streamline tasks like lesson planning, email drafting, and document summarization. Students will also benefit from AI support for research, writing, and studying across applications like Docs, Gmail, and Slides, all while adhering to Google&apos;s privacy commitments for education.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google for Education</tools>
		
		<tools>Google AI</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/gemini-in-workspace-education.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/gemini-in-workspace-education.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - January 30, 2026</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace Weekly Recap for January 30, 2026, unveiled key enhancements including improved Smart Chips and templates in Google Docs, refined conditional formatting and pivot table controls in Google Sheets, and new presenter tools for Google Slides. Significant AI integration was noted with Google Meet gaining AI-powered noise cancellation and expanded live captions, while Gemini provided new summarization in Docs, email drafting in Gmail, and Q&amp;A in Sheets. Security was also boosted with enhanced suspicious activity alerts in Google Drive and new DLP policies via the Google Admin Console.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Admin Console</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-30-2026_0645067218.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-30-2026_0645067218.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>January Workspace Drop: SOTA AI avatars in Vids, deeper insights in the Gemini app, and new app integrations in Chat</title>
        <description>The January Workspace Drop introduces significant AI-powered enhancements across Google Workspace, prominently featuring Gemini integration in Google Docs, Sheets, Slides, Gmail, Meet, and Chat, enabling features like &quot;Help me write&quot; in Docs and AI-powered summarization in Chat. Updates also boost productivity with new organizing features and improved search in Google Drive, smart fill for data cleanup in Google Sheets, and enhanced collaboration tools in Google Meet&apos;s companion mode and picture-in-picture. These advancements aim to streamline workflows, enhance data management, and improve security within the Workspace ecosystem.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/january-workspace-drop</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/january-workspace-drop</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Maximize output, minimize effort: Google Workspace with Gemini helps you move work forward in meetings</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is making Gemini&apos;s AI capabilities generally available to all paying customers, significantly enhancing meeting productivity with features like &quot;Take notes for me&quot; in Google Meet, which automatically generates summaries, key points, and action items. This integration also introduces &quot;Meet Companion Mode&quot; for improved participation and &quot;Translate in Google Meet&quot; for real-time multi-language captions, all built on Google&apos;s responsible AI principles to ensure data privacy and security. These AI-powered tools connect seamlessly with other Workspace apps, including Docs, Sheets, and Slides, to streamline workflows across various business and education editions.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/google-workspace-with-gemini-helps-you-move-work-forward-in-meetings</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/google-workspace-with-gemini-helps-you-move-work-forward-in-meetings</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Editing password-protected Microsoft Office files directly in Google Drive</title>
        <description>Google Drive now allows users to open, edit, and save password-protected Microsoft Office files (DOCX, XLSX, PPTX) directly within Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides on both web and mobile (iOS/Android). This update streamlines collaboration by removing the need to remove password protection, enhancing productivity and security for shared documents. This feature enables real-time co-editing and version control without compromising file integrity.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/edit-password-protected-office-files-google-drive.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/edit-password-protected-office-files-google-drive.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Manage Apple Intelligence Writing Tools in Google Workspace iOS apps</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing new administrative controls to manage Apple&apos;s Scribble feature within Workspace applications on iOS devices. This update allows administrators to enable or disable the use of Apple Pencil&apos;s handwriting-to-text functionality for end-users when interacting with Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides on managed iPhones and iPads. The feature aims to provide IT departments with enhanced oversight regarding data input methods into critical business applications, balancing productivity with compliance and security needs.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/manage-apple-writing-tools-workspace-ios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/manage-apple-writing-tools-workspace-ios.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Beyond the hype: 5 practical ways to use AI-powered visual content at work</title>
        <description>This Google Workspace blog post details five practical applications of AI in visual content, showcasing how generative AI features enhance productivity and collaboration across various industries. It highlights AI&apos;s role in streamlining content creation within Google Slides, intelligent organization in Google Photos, and dynamic presentations in Google Meet, aiding teams from marketing to education. These AI-powered tools empower users to quickly generate professional-quality visuals, summarize information, and improve content accessibility, making visual communication more impactful and efficient.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Photos</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/beyond-the-hype-5-practical-ways-to-use-ai-powered-visual-content</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/beyond-the-hype-5-practical-ways-to-use-ai-powered-visual-content</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>November Workspace Drop: Nano Banana Pro in Slides, Vids, and the Gemini app, plus AI to make meetings more impactful</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing a suite of new AI-powered features, including Google Vids, an AI-powered video creation app to generate scripts and storyboards from scratch, set to launch in Workspace Labs in 2024. Google Slides will gain a &apos;Help me visualize&apos; feature for generative AI image creation and Gemini integration for drafting, while Google Meet receives background music and enhanced audio capabilities, and Google Docs sees smart chip improvements. These updates aim to significantly boost productivity and creativity across the Workspace ecosystem.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/november-workspace-drop-nano-banana-pro-in-slides-vids-and-more</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/november-workspace-drop-nano-banana-pro-in-slides-vids-and-more</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Data classification labels visible in more places across Google Drive</title>
        <description>Google Drive is enhancing data security and user awareness by making data classification labels, previously admin-facing, visible directly to end-users on files in Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides. This feature, available for Workspace Enterprise Plus, Education Standard, and Education Plus customers, aims to promote responsible data handling by clearly indicating sensitivity levels like &quot;Confidential&quot; or &quot;Internal.&quot; The rollout begins immediately for Rapid Release domains and December 9, 2025, for Scheduled Release.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/data-classification-labels-visible-google-drive.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/data-classification-labels-visible-google-drive.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Collaborate seamlessly across Google Workspace and Egnyte</title>
        <description>Google Workspace has launched an enhanced integration with Egnyte, allowing users to seamlessly access, edit, and collaborate on Egnyte files directly from Google Workspace applications such as Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides. This streamlines workflows for organizations leveraging both platforms, fostering greater productivity and ensuring data consistency. The feature is rolling out to all Google Workspace customers, with a full deployment expected by December 9, 2025.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/collaborate-across-google-workspace-and-egnyte.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/collaborate-across-google-workspace-and-egnyte.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Generate presentations in the Gemini app</title>
        <description>The Gemini app is now capable of generating full presentations from text prompts, allowing users to quickly create professional-looking slideshows. This AI-powered feature streamlines content creation for pitches, reports, and educational materials, significantly reducing the time and effort required to design impactful presentations.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:52:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/generate-presentations-in-gemini-app.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/generate-presentations-in-gemini-app.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Summarize shared files with Gemini in Google Chat, now available on mobile </title>
        <description>Gemini Chat on mobile devices now allows users to summarize files directly from Google Drive, including Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides, providing quick access to document insights on the go. This enhancement, available from October 28, 2025, significantly improves mobile productivity and information retrieval efficiency for Workspace users.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/summarize-files-gemini-chat-on-mobile.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/summarize-files-gemini-chat-on-mobile.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Enterprise-grade Gemini is now available for teams of all sizes with Google Workspace</title>
        <description>Google has announced Gemini for Google Workspace, an AI assistant seamlessly integrated into applications like Gmail, Docs, Sheets, and Slides, designed to enhance productivity and creativity. This integration allows users to draft emails, generate content, analyze data, and create presentations more efficiently, leveraging advanced generative AI capabilities across the suite.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-google-workspace</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-google-workspace</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Use Nano Banana to edit images in Google Slides and Vids</title>
        <description>Gemini, Google Slides, and Google Vids are integrating &quot;Nano Banana&quot; image editing capabilities, providing advanced AI-powered tools for manipulating images directly within these applications. Rolling out from September 23, 2025, this feature allows users to easily resize, remove backgrounds, and apply creative edits, significantly enhancing visual content creation.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/nano-banana-image-editing-gemini-slides-vids.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/nano-banana-image-editing-gemini-slides-vids.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>September Workspace Drop: Nano Banana in Slides, shareable Gems, new Vids features, and more!</title>
        <description>The September Google Workspace drop introduces new AI-powered features across the suite, including Nano Banana in Google Slides for enhanced presentation design, advanced Gemini capabilities, and new video editing features in Google Vids. These updates aim to boost creativity and productivity, enabling users to generate content, summarize information, and create engaging visuals more efficiently.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:09:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/september-workspace-drop-nano-banana-in-slides-gems-vids-features-and-more</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/september-workspace-drop-nano-banana-in-slides-gems-vids-features-and-more</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Create videos from your existing Google Slides presentations using Gemini in Google Vids</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Vids now allows users to create videos directly from Google Slides presentations, transforming static content into dynamic visual narratives. Rolling out from September 16, 2025, this feature streamlines video production for presentations, marketing, and educational content, leveraging AI for smooth transitions and compelling storytelling.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/create-videos-from-slides-gemini-in-vids.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/create-videos-from-slides-gemini-in-vids.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Use Gemini to refine text in Slides</title>
        <description>Gemini is now integrated into Google Slides to help users refine text, offering AI-powered suggestions for clarity, conciseness, and tone. Rolling out from August 19, 2025, this feature enhances presentation quality and efficiency by assisting users in crafting impactful content directly within their slides.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/use-gemini-to-refine-text-in-slides.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/use-gemini-to-refine-text-in-slides.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - September 5, 2025</title>
        <description>The Weekly Recap for September 5, 2025, highlights Gemini&apos;s ability to refine text in Google Slides and create videos from Slides in Google Vids. It also covers the introduction of Google AI Pro for Education and a new document scanning UI in Google Drive mobile, showcasing advancements in AI-powered content creation, education, and mobile productivity.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace for Education</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/weekly-recap-09-05-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/weekly-recap-09-05-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>&apos;Help me create&apos; in Google Vids now includes support for Google Slides</title>
        <description>Google Vids now allows users to create videos by directly importing content from Google Slides presentations, streamlining the process of transforming static content into dynamic video. Rolling out from August 19, 2025, this integration is useful for presentations, marketing, and educational materials, enhancing multimedia content creation.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/create-in-google-vids-with-slides.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/create-in-google-vids-with-slides.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Arrow keys now move an object by a pixel distance in Google Slides</title>
        <description>Google Slides is introducing a precision editing feature that allows users to move objects by a single pixel using arrow keys, enhancing design control. Rolling out from August 5, 2025, this update significantly improves the ability to fine-tune visual layouts and alignment in presentations, catering to detailed design needs and improving overall presentation quality.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/move-object-one-pixel-google-slides.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/move-object-one-pixel-google-slides.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Recap - August 15, 2025</title>
        <description>The Weekly Recap for August 18, 2025, highlights app access control request approval and the ability to replace or expand image backgrounds in Slides and Vids. It also covers sorting notes in Google Keep for Android, adding events to Gmail and Calendar via Gemini on mobile, and NotebookLM Gems LTI integration, detailing advancements in security, AI visual editing, mobile organization, and educational AI.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Keep</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Calendar</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-august-18-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-august-18-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Adding AI image editing features to Google Slides and Google Vids</title>
        <description>Google Slides and Google Vids are integrating AI-powered features to replace and expand image backgrounds, allowing for creative visual adjustments. Rolling out from August 12, 2025, this feature simplifies complex image manipulation tasks, enabling users to quickly customize visuals for presentations and videos without requiring advanced graphic design skills.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/replace-expand-image-background-slides-vids.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/replace-expand-image-background-slides-vids.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>New study tools in the Gemini app to help you learn more effectively</title>
        <description>Gemini is integrating new study tools into Google Workspace, allowing students to generate quizzes, study guides, and flashcards directly from Google Docs, Google Slides, and PDFs. This feature, available for Gemini for Google Workspace Education upgrades and the Gemini add-on, aims to enhance learning and preparation for exams by making study material creation more efficient.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini for Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/gemini-study-tools.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/gemini-study-tools.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>NotebookLM is now available to all education users</title>
        <description>NotebookLM, an AI-powered note-taking and research assistant, is now generally available to all Google Workspace users globally, expanding beyond its initial beta for Education customers. This tool allows users to upload documents, PDFs, and Google Slides to generate summaries, outlines, and ask questions, enhancing productivity and knowledge management.</description>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/notebooklm-is-now-available-to-all.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/notebooklm-is-now-available-to-all.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Search for embedded content in Google Sites</title>
        <description>Google Sites is enhancing its search capabilities to include embedded content, allowing users to find information within embedded Google Docs, Sheets, Slides, and other files. This update improves discoverability and efficiency when searching for specific information within a Google Site.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sites</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/search-for-embedded-content-in-google-sites.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/search-for-embedded-content-in-google-sites.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Gems are now available in the side panel of Google Workspace apps</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing &quot;Gems&quot; in the side panel of various apps, providing quick access to generative AI capabilities powered by Gemini directly within the user&apos;s workflow. This integration allows users to leverage AI for drafting, summarizing, and brainstorming without leaving their current Google Docs, Sheets, or Slides documents.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/gems-in-the-side-panel-of-google-workspace-apps.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/gems-in-the-side-panel-of-google-workspace-apps.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Gemini app is now available to all education users</title>
        <description>The Gemini app is now available for all Google Workspace for Education users across all editions, providing advanced AI capabilities for drafting, summarizing, and brainstorming directly within their workflow. This wide rollout aims to empower educators and students with generative AI tools to enhance learning and productivity.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini app</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace for Education</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/the-gemini-app-is-now-available-for-all-google-workspace-for-education-users.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/the-gemini-app-is-now-available-for-all-google-workspace-for-education-users.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Create a Google Vid from Google Slides</title>
        <description>Google Vids, the AI-powered video creation app, now allows users to directly create videos from Google Slides presentations, leveraging AI to transform static content into dynamic visual narratives. This feature streamlines the production of educational and business videos, making it easier to repurpose existing materials.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/create-google-vid-from-google-slides.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/create-google-vid-from-google-slides.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - June 13, 2025</title>
        <description>Google Workspace Release Notes for June 13, 2025, highlight the availability of the Gemini app for all Google Workspace for Education users and expanded language support for Gemini in Google Sheets for chart generation. Other updates include new data migration log events in the Admin console, the ability to create Google Vids from Google Slides, and customizable caption styling for Google Meet.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini app</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Admin console</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace for Education</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/release-notes-06-13-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/release-notes-06-13-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>May Workspace feature drop: New AI features for better collaboration and research, plus NotebookLM Mind Maps</title>
        <description>The May Google Workspace feature drop introduces a suite of new AI capabilities, enhancing productivity across applications like Gmail, Docs, and Slides. These updates include advanced drafting features, intelligent summaries, and improved content generation with Gemini, designed to streamline workflows and foster creativity for users in their daily tasks.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 19:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/may-workspace-feature-drop-new-ai-features</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/may-workspace-feature-drop-new-ai-features</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>New ways Workspace with Gemini helps you do your best work — every day</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing new features and enhancements, particularly with Gemini integration, designed to empower users to do their best work through advanced AI assistance. These updates streamline tasks like drafting documents in Google Docs, analyzing data in Google Sheets, and generating presentations in Google Slides, enabling users to focus on higher-value activities and foster greater creativity.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/new-ways-to-do-your-best-work</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/new-ways-to-do-your-best-work</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Help, not hype: AI built for how you actually work</title>
        <description>Google emphasizes Gemini&apos;s practical application for &apos;help, not hype,&apos; showcasing how its AI capabilities genuinely assist users within Google Workspace applications. Gemini&apos;s integration streamlines daily tasks such as drafting emails in Gmail, summarizing documents in Google Docs, and generating ideas for presentations, providing tangible productivity benefits and enabling users to focus on meaningful work.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-help-not-hype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-help-not-hype</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace apps for Gmail, Google Drive, Google Docs, Calendar, Keep, and Tasks are now generally available for the Gemini app</title>
        <description>Google Workspace applications are now generally available within the Gemini app, allowing users to seamlessly interact with Docs, Sheets, and Slides content through Gemini&apos;s AI interface. This integration provides a unified experience for leveraging generative AI across core Workspace tools, enhancing productivity and content creation.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini app</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/google-workspace-apps-are-now-generally-available-for-the-gemini-app.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/google-workspace-apps-are-now-generally-available-for-the-gemini-app.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Start a conversation with Gemini in the side panel of Google Drive about specific files</title>
        <description>Google Drive now allows users to start conversations with Gemini directly about specific files like Docs, Sheets, Slides, and PDFs, leveraging the file&apos;s content for context. Gemini can summarize documents, answer questions, and provide insights, enhancing productivity and understanding of file contents. This feature is available to Workspace users with Gemini Business, Enterprise, or Education upgrades, and Gemini Advanced subscribers, with a gradual rollout from May 2, 2025.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/start-conversation-with-gemini-in-drive-about-specific-files.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/start-conversation-with-gemini-in-drive-about-specific-files.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Because you asked: My favorite ways to use Gemini at work</title>
        <description>This article highlights favorite practical ways to use Gemini in daily work within Google Workspace, focusing on boosting personal productivity and streamlining common tasks. Examples include generating professional emails in Gmail, summarizing long documents in Google Docs, brainstorming ideas for presentations, and quickly extracting key information from various sources, making workflows more efficient and less time-consuming.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 19:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/because-you-asked-my-favorite-ways-use-gemini-work</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/because-you-asked-my-favorite-ways-use-gemini-work</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Enhance Your Organization’s Security with Out-of-Domain File Warnings in Google Workspace</title>
        <description>Google Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides are introducing new out-of-domain file warnings to enhance data security for Google Workspace users. These warnings will alert users when they open files originating from outside their organization&apos;s trusted domain, helping to prevent accidental data leakage. This feature, gradually rolling out from April 24, 2025, is particularly beneficial for users leveraging Advanced Protection Program or strict Workspace security settings.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/out-of-domain-file-warnings-for-drive-docs-sheets-slides-files.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/out-of-domain-file-warnings-for-drive-docs-sheets-slides-files.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - April 25, 2025</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace release notes for April 25, 2025, announced several updates, including the expansion of NotebookLM&apos;s Audio Overviews to 35 new languages and the introduction of out-of-domain file warnings in Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides for enhanced security. Additionally, Google Vids is now available for Business Starter, Enterprise Starter, and Nonprofits editions, while Gmail users can enjoy new emoji reactions.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/release-notes-04-25-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/release-notes-04-25-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>April Workspace feature drop: New AI features across Gemini, Chat, Gmail, and Slides to boost your productivity</title>
        <description>The April Google Workspace feature drop introduces new AI enhancements across Gemini, Google Chat, Gmail, and Google Slides, aiming to boost productivity and collaboration. Updates include smarter drafting in Gmail, AI-powered summaries in Chat, and advanced content generation in Slides, enabling users to streamline workflows and create compelling content more efficiently.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/april-workspace-feature-drop-new-ai-features-across-gemini-chat-gmail-and-slides</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/april-workspace-feature-drop-new-ai-features-across-gemini-chat-gmail-and-slides</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Introducing even more high-quality Google Slides templates to elevate your presentations</title>
        <description>Google Slides is significantly expanding its template gallery with the addition of even more high-quality, modern templates designed to facilitate the creation of professional and engaging presentations. This update provides Google Workspace users with a wider array of design options and layouts. The new templates are available to all Google Workspace users, enhancing productivity and visual appeal.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/even-more-high-quality-google-slides-templates.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/even-more-high-quality-google-slides-templates.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - April 18, 2025</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace release notes for April 18, 2025, announced the general availability of data classification labels for Gmail, offering enhanced security. New high-quality templates were added to Google Slides, and Google Classroom gained new student group capabilities. The new Frontline Plus SKU was introduced with enhanced security and AI features, and Google Meet expanded language support for &quot;Take notes for me,&quot; recorded captions, and meeting transcripts.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Classroom</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/release-notes-04-18-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/release-notes-04-18-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>MAS gets more out of its creative workflows using Google Workspace with Gemini</title>
        <description>MAS, a global apparel and textile manufacturer, is leveraging Gemini within Google Workspace to significantly enhance its creative workflows, allowing designers to generate ideas and refine concepts more efficiently. This AI integration helps MAS streamline the design process, accelerate content creation, and improve collaboration across its teams, leading to faster product development cycles and increased innovation in a competitive industry.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/mas-gets-more-out-its-creative-workflows-using-gemini</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/mas-gets-more-out-its-creative-workflows-using-gemini</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Creating visually stunning presentations in Google Slides just got easier</title>
        <description>Google Slides is introducing new AI-powered features and design tools to make creating visually stunning presentations easier and more efficient within Google Workspace. These enhancements include intelligent layout suggestions, improved image and video integration, and advanced text formatting options, empowering users to produce professional and engaging presentations with less effort.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/creating-visually-stunning-presentations-google-slides-just-got-easier</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/creating-visually-stunning-presentations-google-slides-just-got-easier</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>New sidebar with design elements in Google Slides makes building presentations easier</title>
        <description>Google Slides is rolling out a redesigned sidebar featuring new design elements to enhance the presentation creation process. This update aims to streamline user workflow by providing easier access to tools for formatting, layout, and content insertion. The improved user interface is available to all Google Workspace users, making professional presentation design more intuitive and efficient.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/new-sidebar-with-design-elements-in-google-slides.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/new-sidebar-with-design-elements-in-google-slides.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - March 28, 2025</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace release notes for March 28, 2025, introduced dynamic layouts for Google Meet and additional language support for Gemini in Drive&apos;s PDF viewer. Google Slides gained proportional scaling for objects, while Google Drive received new nudges for Gemini, and Gmail&apos;s &quot;Help me write&quot; expanded to more languages. Google Classroom&apos;s mobile app also expanded language support, and Google Drive now runs on ARM-compatible Windows PCs. Lastly, Google Vids received new &quot;Help me create&quot; capabilities.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Classroom</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/release-notes-03-28-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/release-notes-03-28-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>March Workspace feature drop: More effective meetings, AI features for Vids, and more language capabilities</title>
        <description>The March Google Workspace feature drop brings new AI capabilities and enhancements across various applications, significantly boosting productivity and collaboration. Key updates include smarter drafting in Gmail, improved data analysis in Google Sheets, and advanced content generation with Gemini, designed to streamline workflows and foster creativity for users.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/march-workspace-feature-drop</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/march-workspace-feature-drop</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Slides introduces proportional scaling for objects to maintain visual clarity</title>
        <description>Google Slides has introduced proportional scaling for objects, such as images, shapes, and text boxes, which now scale proportionally by default when dragged from their corners. Users can hold the Shift key to override this behavior. This enhancement simplifies design consistency and makes it easier for all Google Workspace users to create professional-looking presentations.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/proportional-scaling-objects-in-google-slides.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/proportional-scaling-objects-in-google-slides.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - March 21, 2025</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace release notes for March 21, 2025, announced new features including contextual smart replies for Business/Enterprise customers and enhancements to NotebookLM. Gemini integrations expanded with new languages for the Chat and Slides side panels, and a new &quot;Canvas&quot; interface for the Gemini App was introduced, alongside summaries of shared Workspace files in Google Chat and a new Gemini-powered summary building block in Google Docs. Gmail DLP was updated with sensitive content snippets and instant rule application, NotebookLM gained context-aware access, and a beta launched for converting client-side encrypted documents after Vault or Takeout export.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vault</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Takeout</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/release-notes-03-21-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/release-notes-03-21-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>5 ways to help your small business thrive with Google Drive</title>
        <description>Google Drive offers five essential ways to help small businesses thrive, focusing on secure collaboration, efficient file management, and robust data backup. These include easy sharing, version control, offline access, integration with Google Workspace apps, and reliable cloud storage, empowering small businesses to improve productivity and ensure business continuity.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 19:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/five-ways-help-your-small-business-thrive-google-drive</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/five-ways-help-your-small-business-thrive-google-drive</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Use Gemini in the side panel of Google Slides in even more languages</title>
        <description>Gemini&apos;s integration within the Google Slides side panel is now available in many new languages, allowing users to leverage AI assistance for presentation tasks like generating slides and writing content in diverse linguistic contexts. This significantly enhances productivity and creative potential for a global audience. The feature is available to Google Workspace Business, Enterprise, Education Plus, and Teaching and Learning Upgrade customers.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/gemini-in-slides-side-panel-available-in-many-new-languages.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/gemini-in-slides-side-panel-available-in-many-new-languages.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>See summaries of shared Google Docs, Slides, or Sheets files directly in Google Chat</title>
        <description>Google Chat will now automatically generate summaries of shared Google Workspace files, including Docs, Sheets, Slides, and PDFs, when they are linked in a chat conversation. This AI-powered feature enables users to quickly grasp the essence of a document without leaving Google Chat, significantly improving workflow efficiency. The feature is available for Google Workspace Business, Enterprise, Education Plus, and Teaching and Learning Upgrade customers.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/summaries-of-shared-workspace-files-in-google-chat.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/summaries-of-shared-workspace-files-in-google-chat.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Use Gemini in the side panel of Workspace apps in four more languages</title>
        <description>The Gemini side panel, integrated across various Google Workspace applications such as Docs, Sheets, and Slides, is expanding its language support to include four additional languages. This enhancement makes AI assistance more accessible and useful for a wider global audience of non-English speaking users. This continuous language expansion improves the overall user experience and productivity within Workspace.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/four-additional-languages-supported-in-gemini-side-panel.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/four-additional-languages-supported-in-gemini-side-panel.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - March 7, 2025</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace release notes for March 7, 2025, detailed updates including enhancements for generating meeting backgrounds with Gemini and the Gemini in Slides side panel supporting seven new languages. A Salesforce extension for Gemini in Gmail was introduced to streamline CRM interactions, and Google Calendar received improvements for better interoperability with Outlook.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Calendar</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/release-notes-03-07-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/release-notes-03-07-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Use Gemini in the side panel of Google Slides in seven new languages</title>
        <description>Gemini&apos;s integration within the Google Slides side panel is expanding its language support to include seven new languages, allowing users to leverage AI assistance for presentation tasks like generating slides and writing content in diverse linguistic contexts. This significantly enhances productivity and creative potential for a global audience. The feature is available to Google Workspace Business, Enterprise, Education Plus, and Teaching and Learning Upgrade customers.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/gemini-in-slides-side-panel-seven-new-languages.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/gemini-in-slides-side-panel-seven-new-languages.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Workspace feature drop: 4 new ways to help you do your best work</title>
        <description>The February Google Workspace feature drop introduces new AI enhancements and productivity features across its applications, aimed at improving collaboration and efficiency. Key updates include smarter content suggestions in Docs and Slides, advanced search capabilities, and refinements to existing AI tools like Gemini, designed to help users streamline tasks and foster creativity.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/february-workspace-feature-drop</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/february-workspace-feature-drop</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Sundogs rises to meet creative challenges at scale using Google Workspace with Gemini</title>
        <description>Sundogs, a creative agency, is using Google Workspace with Gemini to meet creative challenges at scale, significantly enhancing its content creation and client communication workflows. Gemini helps Sundogs&apos; designers and marketers generate compelling copy, brainstorm ideas, and summarize client feedback, enabling faster project turnaround and greater creative output while maintaining high-quality standards.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/sundogs-rises-meet-creative-challenges-scale-using-google-workspace-gemini</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/sundogs-rises-meet-creative-challenges-scale-using-google-workspace-gemini</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace enables the future of AI-powered work for every business</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is empowering businesses with new AI capabilities, primarily through Gemini, designed to enhance productivity, streamline operations, and foster innovation across all sizes of organizations. These AI features are integrated into core applications like Gmail, Docs, and Sheets, enabling users to automate routine tasks, generate high-quality content, and gain deeper insights from their data.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/empowering-businesses-with-ai</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/empowering-businesses-with-ai</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>4 ways Gemini for Workspace can help sellers and marketers spend more time doing what they do best</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Workspace offers four key ways to help sellers and marketers focus on their core competencies: automating content creation for emails and presentations, summarizing market research, analyzing sales data, and personalizing customer communications. This AI integration allows them to streamline routine tasks, enhance outreach strategies, and gain deeper insights, ultimately boosting productivity and customer engagement.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/4-ways-gemini-workspace-can-help-sellers-and-marketers-spend-more-time-doing-what-they-do-best</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/4-ways-gemini-workspace-can-help-sellers-and-marketers-spend-more-time-doing-what-they-do-best</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>