<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google Sheets Knowledge  - RSS</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Get higher access to advanced AI in Google Workspace</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is significantly expanding access to its AI-powered features, including the Gemini model, across its suite of productivity applications. This initiative aims to bring enhanced capabilities, such as automated content generation in Google Docs, data analysis in Google Sheets, and presentation creation in Google Slides, to a broader range of users and regions globally. The expansion underscores Google&apos;s commitment to integrating advanced artificial intelligence directly into daily workflows to boost productivity and foster creativity for its users.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/google-workspace-ai-expanded-access.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/google-workspace-ai-expanded-access.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Expanding access to select Google Vids features for all users</title>
        <description>Google Vids, the AI-powered video creation app within Google Workspace, is expanding access to more Workspace customers, including those on Business Standard and Plus, Enterprise Starter, Standard, Plus, and Education Plus tiers. This tool utilizes generative AI to assist with scriptwriting, storyboarding, and raw cut generation, streamlining the creation of business videos for various purposes. It integrates seamlessly with existing Workspace applications like Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides, enhancing collaboration and content management.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/expanding-access-to-select-google-vids.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/02/expanding-access-to-select-google-vids.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - January 30, 2026</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace Weekly Recap for January 30, 2026, unveiled key enhancements including improved Smart Chips and templates in Google Docs, refined conditional formatting and pivot table controls in Google Sheets, and new presenter tools for Google Slides. Significant AI integration was noted with Google Meet gaining AI-powered noise cancellation and expanded live captions, while Gemini provided new summarization in Docs, email drafting in Gmail, and Q&amp;A in Sheets. Security was also boosted with enhanced suspicious activity alerts in Google Drive and new DLP policies via the Google Admin Console.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Admin Console</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-30-2026_0645067218.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-30-2026_0645067218.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>January Workspace Drop: SOTA AI avatars in Vids, deeper insights in the Gemini app, and new app integrations in Chat</title>
        <description>The January Workspace Drop introduces significant AI-powered enhancements across Google Workspace, prominently featuring Gemini integration in Google Docs, Sheets, Slides, Gmail, Meet, and Chat, enabling features like &quot;Help me write&quot; in Docs and AI-powered summarization in Chat. Updates also boost productivity with new organizing features and improved search in Google Drive, smart fill for data cleanup in Google Sheets, and enhanced collaboration tools in Google Meet&apos;s companion mode and picture-in-picture. These advancements aim to streamline workflows, enhance data management, and improve security within the Workspace ecosystem.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/january-workspace-drop</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/january-workspace-drop</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The 5-minute data dashboard: Visualize and analyze with Google Sheets</title>
        <description>This Google Workspace blog post outlines how to create a data dashboard in under five minutes using Google Sheets&apos; new AI-powered &quot;smart fill&quot; and &quot;smart cleanup&quot; features. These capabilities automate data preparation and organization, enabling users to quickly transform raw data from sources like Google Analytics into visual, actionable insights. The process simplifies data analysis, making it accessible for users to build dashboards without extensive manual data manipulation.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Analytics</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/5-minute-data-dashboard-visualize-and-analyze-with-sheets</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/5-minute-data-dashboard-visualize-and-analyze-with-sheets</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - January 23, 2026</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace weekly recap for January 23, 2026, highlights several key updates including enhanced Google Docs version history, AI-driven pivot table insights in Google Sheets, and new background customization options for Google Meet. Additionally, the recap covers improved security alerts for Google Drive sharing and expanded Gemini integrations across Workspace applications. These updates collectively aim to boost productivity, security, and collaboration for users across the enterprise.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Admin Console</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-23-2026.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-23-2026.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - January 16, 2026</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace Weekly Recap for January 16, 2026, highlighted significant updates including enhanced AI capabilities in Google Docs for summarizing and drafting, and improved collaboration features in Google Sheets with better version history and comment threading. Additionally, security enhancements were rolled out for Google Drive, focusing on advanced data loss prevention, alongside new integrations for Google Meet and ongoing developments with Gemini for Workspace.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Calendar</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-16-2026.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/weekly-recap-01-16-2026.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Flow now available as an additional Google service for Workspace customers</title>
        <description>Google has introduced &quot;Flow&quot; as a new service within Google Workspace, designed to streamline and automate workflows by integrating data and tasks across various applications. This new tool offers a visual workflow builder, pre-built templates, and conditional logic, enabling Workspace customers to boost efficiency and reduce manual errors. Admins can manage &quot;Flow&quot; through the Google Admin console, with a phased rollout planned for all Workspace editions.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Admin console</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/flow-available-additional-google-service-workspace.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/flow-available-additional-google-service-workspace.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Maximize output, minimize effort: Google Workspace with Gemini helps you move work forward in meetings</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is making Gemini&apos;s AI capabilities generally available to all paying customers, significantly enhancing meeting productivity with features like &quot;Take notes for me&quot; in Google Meet, which automatically generates summaries, key points, and action items. This integration also introduces &quot;Meet Companion Mode&quot; for improved participation and &quot;Translate in Google Meet&quot; for real-time multi-language captions, all built on Google&apos;s responsible AI principles to ensure data privacy and security. These AI-powered tools connect seamlessly with other Workspace apps, including Docs, Sheets, and Slides, to streamline workflows across various business and education editions.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/google-workspace-with-gemini-helps-you-move-work-forward-in-meetings</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/google-workspace-with-gemini-helps-you-move-work-forward-in-meetings</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Editing password-protected Microsoft Office files directly in Google Drive</title>
        <description>Google Drive now allows users to open, edit, and save password-protected Microsoft Office files (DOCX, XLSX, PPTX) directly within Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides on both web and mobile (iOS/Android). This update streamlines collaboration by removing the need to remove password protection, enhancing productivity and security for shared documents. This feature enables real-time co-editing and version control without compromising file integrity.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/edit-password-protected-office-files-google-drive.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/edit-password-protected-office-files-google-drive.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Manage Apple Intelligence Writing Tools in Google Workspace iOS apps</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing new administrative controls to manage Apple&apos;s Scribble feature within Workspace applications on iOS devices. This update allows administrators to enable or disable the use of Apple Pencil&apos;s handwriting-to-text functionality for end-users when interacting with Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides on managed iPhones and iPads. The feature aims to provide IT departments with enhanced oversight regarding data input methods into critical business applications, balancing productivity with compliance and security needs.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/manage-apple-writing-tools-workspace-ios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2026/01/manage-apple-writing-tools-workspace-ios.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Boost your agency&apos;s efficiency: Take Google Workspace for a test drive</title>
        <description>Google Cloud is offering public sector organizations a 60-day, no-cost &quot;Google Workspace Test Drive&quot; program to experience its capabilities for digital transformation and hybrid work. This program highlights secure collaboration, AI features like Gemini for Workspace, data loss prevention, and FedRAMP High authorization, allowing government agencies to evaluate tools like Gmail, Docs, Sheets, and Meet. The initiative aims to provide hands-on experience and support from Google Cloud experts to demonstrate enhanced productivity and compliance.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Cloud</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini for Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/public-sector/take-google-workspace-for-a-test-drive</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/public-sector/take-google-workspace-for-a-test-drive</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace is the “new default” for The Carbon Group&apos;s fractional C-suite services</title>
        <description>The Carbon Group, an Australian financial services firm, transitioned 180 employees from Microsoft to Google Workspace, standardizing on tools like Google Sheets, Drive, Meet, Gmail, and Docs. This move significantly improved collaboration, security, and productivity across their 13 offices, enabling real-time file sharing, streamlined communication, and efficient onboarding of new team members. The shift has made Google Workspace the company&apos;s default platform, centralizing operations and enhancing the hybrid work experience.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/google-workspace-is-the-new-default-for-the-carbon-group</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/google-workspace-is-the-new-default-for-the-carbon-group</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Now available: Create AI agents to automate work with Google Workspace Studio</title>
        <description>Workspace Studio, an AI-powered hub, is now available for Google Workspace customers to discover, manage, and create generative AI solutions and custom workflows. It integrates with tools like AppSheet and Apps Script, enabling businesses to leverage AI to automate tasks and enhance productivity within Google Sheets, Docs, and other Workspace apps.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>AppSheet</tools>
		
		<tools>Apps Script</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/12/workspace-studio.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/12/workspace-studio.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>How Bison Coolers relies on Google to run its family business</title>
        <description>Bison Coolers, a Texas-based family business manufacturing rotomolded coolers, transitioned from a costly Microsoft Exchange setup to Google Workspace to enhance collaboration and reduce IT overhead. Leveraging tools like Gmail, Google Drive, Docs, and Sheets, alongside Google Meet and Chat, the company streamlined communication, enabled remote work, and scaled from three to over 20 employees. This shift significantly improved productivity for traveling sales teams, provided cost savings, and bolstered disaster recovery capabilities for their growing business operations.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Admin console</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/how-bison-coolers-relies-on-google-to-run-its-family-business</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/how-bison-coolers-relies-on-google-to-run-its-family-business</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>November Workspace Drop: Nano Banana Pro in Slides, Vids, and the Gemini app, plus AI to make meetings more impactful</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing a suite of new AI-powered features, including Google Vids, an AI-powered video creation app to generate scripts and storyboards from scratch, set to launch in Workspace Labs in 2024. Google Slides will gain a &apos;Help me visualize&apos; feature for generative AI image creation and Gemini integration for drafting, while Google Meet receives background music and enhanced audio capabilities, and Google Docs sees smart chip improvements. These updates aim to significantly boost productivity and creativity across the Workspace ecosystem.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/november-workspace-drop-nano-banana-pro-in-slides-vids-and-more</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/november-workspace-drop-nano-banana-pro-in-slides-vids-and-more</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Data classification labels visible in more places across Google Drive</title>
        <description>Google Drive is enhancing data security and user awareness by making data classification labels, previously admin-facing, visible directly to end-users on files in Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides. This feature, available for Workspace Enterprise Plus, Education Standard, and Education Plus customers, aims to promote responsible data handling by clearly indicating sensitivity levels like &quot;Confidential&quot; or &quot;Internal.&quot; The rollout begins immediately for Rapid Release domains and December 9, 2025, for Scheduled Release.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/data-classification-labels-visible-google-drive.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/data-classification-labels-visible-google-drive.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Collaborate seamlessly across Google Workspace and Egnyte</title>
        <description>Google Workspace has launched an enhanced integration with Egnyte, allowing users to seamlessly access, edit, and collaborate on Egnyte files directly from Google Workspace applications such as Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides. This streamlines workflows for organizations leveraging both platforms, fostering greater productivity and ensuring data consistency. The feature is rolling out to all Google Workspace customers, with a full deployment expected by December 9, 2025.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/collaborate-across-google-workspace-and-egnyte.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/collaborate-across-google-workspace-and-egnyte.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>From spreadsheet jockey to strategic advisor: My journey with AI-powered Google Sheets</title>
        <description>Nick, a financial analyst, shares his journey using AI, specifically Google Sheets with Gemini integration, to transform his financial modeling and data analysis workflows. He leveraged Gemini to quickly analyze data, extract insights, and generate Apps Script code for automating repetitive tasks like updating P&amp;L statements. This significantly enhanced efficiency and reduced manual effort, allowing him to focus on strategic insights rather than data cleanup.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Apps Script</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/my-journey-with-ai-powered-google-sheets</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/my-journey-with-ai-powered-google-sheets</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Analyze large-scale .csv files in Google Sheets with a new direct-to-BigQuery import</title>
        <description>Google Sheets now enables users to analyze large-scale CSV files stored in Google Drive, supporting datasets up to 10 million cells without impacting the Sheet&apos;s internal cell limit. Rolling out from November 11, 2025, this enhancement allows for efficient data exploration, filtering, sorting, and pivot table creation on massive datasets.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/analyze-large-scale-csv-files-in-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/11/analyze-large-scale-csv-files-in-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - October 31, 2025</title>
        <description>This weekly recap for October 31, 2025, covers recent Google Workspace updates including enhanced writing assistance with Gemini in Google Docs, improvements to Google Chat&apos;s Workday app integration, and more powerful pivot tables in Google Sheets&apos; Connected Sheets. The summary also touches on enhanced admin audit logs and new presentation generation capabilities via Gemini.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 22:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/weekly-recap-10-31-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/weekly-recap-10-31-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>More powerful pivot tables in Connected Sheets</title>
        <description>Google Sheets&apos; Connected Sheets feature is gaining more powerful pivot table capabilities, enabling users to perform advanced data analysis directly on data sourced from BigQuery and other external databases. This enhancement allows for more complex insights and robust reporting without leaving the familiar Sheets interface, boosting productivity for data analysts.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>BigQuery</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:39:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/powerful-pivot-tables-connected-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/powerful-pivot-tables-connected-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Gemini in Google Sheets can now analyze data across multiple tables</title>
        <description>Gemini is integrating with Google Sheets to provide AI-powered data analysis capabilities, allowing users to ask natural language questions about their data and receive insights or formula suggestions. This enhancement democratizes data analysis, making it easier for users of all skill levels to extract meaningful information and trends from their spreadsheets.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/gemini-in-google-sheets-analyze-data.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/gemini-in-google-sheets-analyze-data.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - October 17, 2025</title>
        <description>This weekly recap for October 17, 2025, highlights new features such as AI credit overage controls and billing transparency for admins, enhanced Gmail protection against XS-Search attacks, and Gemini&apos;s new data analysis capabilities in Google Sheets. It also mentions the release of Flashcards in Gemini and new business continuity editions for Google Workspace.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/weekly-recap-10-17-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/weekly-recap-10-17-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Gemini in Google Sheets now tackles multi-step tasks with expanded editing capabilities</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets is receiving expanded editing capabilities, enabling users to modify and refine AI-generated content or formulas more intuitively. This enhancement allows for greater control and customization over AI suggestions, making Gemini a more flexible and powerful co-editor for complex data manipulation and analysis within spreadsheets.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/expanded-editing-capabilities-gemini-in-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/expanded-editing-capabilities-gemini-in-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The AI function in Google Sheets is now enhanced with Google Search results for more up-to-date answers</title>
        <description>Google Sheets is gaining enhanced AI functions powered by Google Search, enabling users to integrate real-time public data and broader web information directly into their spreadsheets. Rolling out from October 21, 2025, this feature allows for more dynamic and informed data analysis, expanding Sheets&apos; utility significantly.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Search</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/enhanced-ai-function-sheets-google-search.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/enhanced-ai-function-sheets-google-search.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Summarize shared files with Gemini in Google Chat, now available on mobile </title>
        <description>Gemini Chat on mobile devices now allows users to summarize files directly from Google Drive, including Google Docs, Sheets, and Slides, providing quick access to document insights on the go. This enhancement, available from October 28, 2025, significantly improves mobile productivity and information retrieval efficiency for Workspace users.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/summarize-files-gemini-chat-on-mobile.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/summarize-files-gemini-chat-on-mobile.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Enterprise-grade Gemini is now available for teams of all sizes with Google Workspace</title>
        <description>Google has announced Gemini for Google Workspace, an AI assistant seamlessly integrated into applications like Gmail, Docs, Sheets, and Slides, designed to enhance productivity and creativity. This integration allows users to draft emails, generate content, analyze data, and create presentations more efficiently, leveraging advanced generative AI capabilities across the suite.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-google-workspace</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-google-workspace</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Looker Connected Sheets Private IP support</title>
        <description>Looker Connected Sheets now supports private IP connections, enabling users to securely access data from Looker instances residing within private networks. Rolling out from October 21, 2025, this feature enhances data security and compliance for enterprises by keeping sensitive information within their internal infrastructure while utilizing Looker&apos;s robust analytics.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Looker</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/looker-connected-sheets-private-ip.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/10/looker-connected-sheets-private-ip.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Configure up to 20 conditional notifications per Google Sheet</title>
        <description>Google Sheets is increasing its limit for conditional notifications to 20 per sheet, enabling users to create more complex and targeted alert systems. Rolling out from September 23, 2025, this enhancement allows for advanced automation in data monitoring and task management within spreadsheets, improving responsiveness to critical data changes.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/up-to-20-conditional-notifications-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/up-to-20-conditional-notifications-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Gemini in Google Sheets now provides smarter, more conversational formula generation</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets is introducing smarter natural language formula generation, allowing users to create complex spreadsheet formulas using everyday language. Rolling out from September 16, 2025, this enhancement democratizes data analysis by making advanced functions accessible to a wider audience, thereby improving productivity and reducing errors.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/smarter-natural-formula-generation-gemini-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/smarter-natural-formula-generation-gemini-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Generate data with AI function in Sheets now available in seven additional languages</title>
        <description>Google Sheets&apos; AI functions are expanding to support new languages, making advanced data analysis capabilities accessible to a broader global audience. Rolling out from September 9, 2025, this enhancement democratizes data processing and formula generation for non-English speaking users, significantly improving productivity worldwide.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/ai-function-google-sheets-new-languages.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/ai-function-google-sheets-new-languages.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Now generally available: Convert your Client-side encrypted Google Sheets after a Vault or Takeout export</title>
        <description>Google Sheets now offers full client-side encryption (CSE) support, providing enhanced data privacy and security for highly sensitive spreadsheet content. Rolling out from September 2, 2025, this feature ensures data is encrypted before leaving the user&apos;s device, offering an additional layer of protection particularly vital for regulated industries.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/client-side-encryption-full-sheets-support.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/client-side-encryption-full-sheets-support.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - September 12, 2025</title>
        <description>The Weekly Recap for September 12, 2025, highlights Gemini summaries on the Drive Home page and NotebookLM&apos;s new flashcards and quizzes for education. It also covers condensed version history in Google Sheets and the beta launch of the Shared Signals Framework, detailing advancements in AI insights, data management, and security.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/weekly-recap-09-12-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/weekly-recap-09-12-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Understand changes more quickly with condensed version history in Sheets</title>
        <description>Google Sheets is introducing a condensed version history feature, simplifying the review and reversion to previous spreadsheet states without sifting through granular changes. Rolling out from August 26, 2025, this enhancement improves collaboration and data integrity by streamlining the management of document revisions.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/condensed-version-history-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/09/condensed-version-history-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Mercer International unlocks $3 million a year in productivity gains using Google Workspace with Gemini</title>
        <description>Mercer International, a global leader in the pulp and lumber industry, has achieved significant productivity gains by implementing Google Workspace with Gemini across its operations. Gemini helps Mercer employees, including CFO Bill Short, automate administrative tasks, streamline communications in Gmail, and summarize complex financial reports, allowing them to focus on strategic analysis and decision-making.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:09:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/mercer-international-productivity-gains-google-workspace-gemini</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/mercer-international-productivity-gains-google-workspace-gemini</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - August 29, 2025</title>
        <description>The Weekly Recap for August 29, 2025, highlights new features such as daily exports for Google Drive, and the ability to convert images to videos with Google Vids. It also covers AI avatars in Vids, transcript-based video editing, and enhanced Gemini features in Google Sheets, showcasing advancements in data management, AI-powered video creation, and spreadsheet intelligence.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-08-29-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-08-29-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>August Workspace Drop: Unlock insights and get up to speed quickly with new AI features in Sheets, NotebookLM, and more!</title>
        <description>The August Google Workspace drop introduces significant AI-powered features, including enhanced capabilities in Google Sheets for data analysis and deeper integration of NotebookLM for advanced research. These updates aim to boost productivity by enabling users to automate data insights, summarize extensive documents, and generate content more efficiently across their daily workflows.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:08:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/august-workspace-drop-ai-features-sheets-notebooklm</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/august-workspace-drop-ai-features-sheets-notebooklm</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Gemini in Google Sheets helps you create dynamic and easily referenced tables</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets is enhancing its capabilities to assist users with data analysis, formula generation, and insight extraction using natural language. Rolling out from August 12, 2025, this feature makes complex spreadsheet tasks more accessible and efficient, significantly improving productivity for a wide range of users.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/gemini-in-google-sheets-helps-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/gemini-in-google-sheets-helps-you.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - August 22, 2025</title>
        <description>The Weekly Recap for August 22, 2025, highlights the ability to edit Google Drive videos directly in Google Vids and new pre-configured appointment booking in Google Calendar. It also covers Gemini Live integration with Calendar, Tasks, and Keep, alongside ServiceNow integration with Google Chat and Sheets, showcasing advancements in video editing, scheduling, AI integration, and enterprise tools.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Calendar</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Tasks</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Keep</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-08-22-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-08-22-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Effortlessly work with ServiceNow data across Google Chat and Sheets</title>
        <description>ServiceNow is integrating with Google Chat and Google Sheets, enabling seamless workflows between IT service management and Workspace collaboration tools. Rolling out from August 5, 2025, this integration allows users to manage service requests, update tickets, and analyze data directly from Chat and Sheets, significantly improving IT efficiency and communication.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/servicenow-google-chat-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/servicenow-google-chat-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Improving the ISEMAIL and ISURL functions in Google Sheets</title>
        <description>Google Sheets is improving the accuracy and functionality of its ISMAIL and ISURL functions, enhancing data validation and processing capabilities. Rolling out from August 5, 2025, this update helps users more reliably identify and work with email addresses and URLs within their spreadsheets, ensuring cleaner and more accurate data.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/improving-isemail-isurl-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/08/improving-isemail-isurl-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Build and deploy a single app across Chat, Gmail, Calendar, Drive and more with the Workspace add-ons framework</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is rolling out the capability for developers to build and deploy a single application that functions seamlessly across Google Chat, Google Docs, and Google Sheets. This new framework aims to streamline development and enhance app functionality within the Google Workspace ecosystem, reducing redundant development efforts for multi-platform integrations.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Cloud</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/build-and-deploy-single-app-across-chat.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/build-and-deploy-single-app-across-chat.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Questrade Financial Group transforms productivity using Google Workspace with Gemini</title>
        <description>Questrade Financial Group, a leading online brokerage, is transforming productivity by integrating Gemini into Google Workspace, enabling its employees to enhance efficiency across various operations. Gemini helps Questrade streamline content creation, summarize complex financial documents, and improve communication, allowing teams to focus more on strategic initiatives and client service within a regulated financial environment.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:07:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/questrade-financial-group-transforms-productivity-gemini-google-workspace</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/questrade-financial-group-transforms-productivity-gemini-google-workspace</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Beyond the prompt: Resources to get started with Workspace with Gemini today</title>
        <description>Google offers comprehensive resources to help users move &apos;beyond the prompt&apos; and master advanced techniques for leveraging Gemini&apos;s full potential within Google Workspace. These resources include guides on prompt engineering, best practices for integrating AI into workflows, and case studies highlighting how Gemini enhances productivity and creativity for various tasks, from drafting emails to analyzing data.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 19:07:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/beyond-the-prompt-resources-gemini</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/beyond-the-prompt-resources-gemini</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Search for embedded content in Google Sites</title>
        <description>Google Sites is enhancing its search capabilities to include embedded content, allowing users to find information within embedded Google Docs, Sheets, Slides, and other files. This update improves discoverability and efficiency when searching for specific information within a Google Site.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Sites</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/search-for-embedded-content-in-google-sites.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/search-for-embedded-content-in-google-sites.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Gems are now available in the side panel of Google Workspace apps</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing &quot;Gems&quot; in the side panel of various apps, providing quick access to generative AI capabilities powered by Gemini directly within the user&apos;s workflow. This integration allows users to leverage AI for drafting, summarizing, and brainstorming without leaving their current Google Docs, Sheets, or Slides documents.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/gems-in-the-side-panel-of-google-workspace-apps.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/07/gems-in-the-side-panel-of-google-workspace-apps.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Push what’s possible with Google AI Ultra for Business</title>
        <description>Google AI Ultra for Business is introduced as a premium tier of Gemini, designed to provide advanced generative AI capabilities tailored for enterprise use cases within Google Workspace. This offering delivers enhanced performance, greater context windows, and robust security features, empowering businesses to tackle complex tasks like advanced data analysis, sophisticated content generation, and intricate workflow automation.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 19:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/google-ai-ultra-for-business</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/google-ai-ultra-for-business</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Generate data with Gemini in Google Sheets</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets now allows users to generate data, such as sample datasets or placeholder information, directly within their spreadsheets using natural language prompts. This feature, available for Gemini for Google Workspace users, streamlines data entry and content creation for analysis and prototyping.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini for Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/generate-data-with-gemini-in-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/generate-data-with-gemini-in-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Equifax embraces secure generative AI with Gemini</title>
        <description>Equifax, a global data, analytics, and technology company, is embracing Gemini for secure innovation across its business units, leveraging its capabilities within Google Workspace. Gemini helps Equifax enhance productivity, streamline data analysis, and accelerate report generation while maintaining stringent security and compliance standards, critical for the financial services industry.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Cloud</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/equifax-embraces-gemini-for-secure-innovation-across-business-units</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/equifax-embraces-gemini-for-secure-innovation-across-business-units</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - June 20, 2025</title>
        <description>Google Workspace Release Notes for June 20, 2025, detail updates including more granular controls for multi-party approvals in admin actions and the rollout of Google AI Ultra for business users. Other highlights cover improved Gemini add-on management in the Admin console, updates to the GitHub App for Google Chat, and expanded AI summaries for shared files in Google Chat.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google AI Ultra</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Admin console</tools>
		
		<tools>GitHub App</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/release-notes-06-20-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/release-notes-06-20-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Gemini app is now available to all education users</title>
        <description>The Gemini app is now available for all Google Workspace for Education users across all editions, providing advanced AI capabilities for drafting, summarizing, and brainstorming directly within their workflow. This wide rollout aims to empower educators and students with generative AI tools to enhance learning and productivity.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini app</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace for Education</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/the-gemini-app-is-now-available-for-all-google-workspace-for-education-users.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/the-gemini-app-is-now-available-for-all-google-workspace-for-education-users.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Generate charts and valuable insights using Gemini in Google Sheets in additional languages </title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets is expanding its language support, allowing users to generate charts and insights from data using natural language prompts in additional languages beyond English. This enhancement aims to make data analysis and visualization more accessible to a global user base.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/more-languages-to-generate-charts-and-insights-with-gemini-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/more-languages-to-generate-charts-and-insights-with-gemini-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - June 13, 2025</title>
        <description>Google Workspace Release Notes for June 13, 2025, highlight the availability of the Gemini app for all Google Workspace for Education users and expanded language support for Gemini in Google Sheets for chart generation. Other updates include new data migration log events in the Admin console, the ability to create Google Vids from Google Slides, and customizable caption styling for Google Meet.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini app</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Admin console</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace for Education</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/release-notes-06-13-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/release-notes-06-13-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>4 ways Gemini in Google Sheets helps small businesses get insights faster</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets offers small businesses four key ways to gain insights faster: automating data organization, generating complex formulas, summarizing data sets, and creating insightful charts. This integration empowers small business owners to streamline financial analysis, inventory management, and customer data reporting, leading to more informed decisions and increased efficiency without requiring extensive data science expertise.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/4-ways-gemini-google-sheets-helps-small-businesses-get-insights-faster</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/4-ways-gemini-google-sheets-helps-small-businesses-get-insights-faster</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Generate fully editable charts using Gemini in Google Sheets</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets now generates fully editable charts, allowing users to customize AI-created visualizations directly within their spreadsheets. This feature provides flexibility and control, making it easier to refine and tailor data representations generated by AI.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/fully-editable-charts-gemini-in-google-sheets.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/06/fully-editable-charts-gemini-in-google-sheets.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Democratizing app development using AppSheet with Gemini</title>
        <description>Google is democratizing app development by integrating Gemini into AppSheet, its no-code development platform, empowering citizen developers to create powerful applications with greater ease and speed. This AI integration allows users to build custom apps by simply describing their needs in natural language, automating complex logic and data connections to enhance business processes across Google Workspace.</description>
		
		<tools>AppSheet</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/democratizing-app-development-using-appsheet-gemini</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/democratizing-app-development-using-appsheet-gemini</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>New ways Workspace with Gemini helps you do your best work — every day</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is introducing new features and enhancements, particularly with Gemini integration, designed to empower users to do their best work through advanced AI assistance. These updates streamline tasks like drafting documents in Google Docs, analyzing data in Google Sheets, and generating presentations in Google Slides, enabling users to focus on higher-value activities and foster greater creativity.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/new-ways-to-do-your-best-work</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/new-ways-to-do-your-best-work</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Help, not hype: AI built for how you actually work</title>
        <description>Google emphasizes Gemini&apos;s practical application for &apos;help, not hype,&apos; showcasing how its AI capabilities genuinely assist users within Google Workspace applications. Gemini&apos;s integration streamlines daily tasks such as drafting emails in Gmail, summarizing documents in Google Docs, and generating ideas for presentations, providing tangible productivity benefits and enabling users to focus on meaningful work.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-help-not-hype</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/gemini-for-help-not-hype</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Supercharging employee experience and reducing routine work with Gemini at ATB Financial</title>
        <description>ATB Financial is supercharging its employee experience and significantly reducing routine work by integrating Gemini into Google Workspace across its operations. Gemini helps employees automate tasks like drafting communications and summarizing reports, allowing them to focus on strategic initiatives and customer engagement, leading to enhanced productivity and job satisfaction within the financial institution.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/supercharging-employee-experience-and-reducing-routine-work-gemini-atb-financial</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/supercharging-employee-experience-and-reducing-routine-work-gemini-atb-financial</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace apps for Gmail, Google Drive, Google Docs, Calendar, Keep, and Tasks are now generally available for the Gemini app</title>
        <description>Google Workspace applications are now generally available within the Gemini app, allowing users to seamlessly interact with Docs, Sheets, and Slides content through Gemini&apos;s AI interface. This integration provides a unified experience for leveraging generative AI across core Workspace tools, enhancing productivity and content creation.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini app</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/google-workspace-apps-are-now-generally-available-for-the-gemini-app.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/google-workspace-apps-are-now-generally-available-for-the-gemini-app.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Use Gemini in Google Sheets to quickly add dropdowns, pivot tables, filters, and more</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Sheets is introducing advanced actions, allowing users to perform complex data manipulations, generate formulas, and automate tasks with natural language commands. This enhancement boosts productivity for data analysis and spreadsheet management, making powerful features more accessible to a wider audience.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/use-gemini-google-sheets-advanced-actions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/use-gemini-google-sheets-advanced-actions.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Fullstory writes collaboration into its culture with Google Workspace and Gemini</title>
        <description>FullStory is fostering a stronger collaboration culture by leveraging Google Workspace with Gemini, enhancing productivity and creative workflows across its global teams. Gemini assists FullStory employees in streamlining content creation, summarizing complex data, and improving communication, allowing them to focus on customer experience insights and product development, leading to more efficient and impactful outcomes.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 21:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/fullstory-collaboration-culture-with-google-workspace-and-gemini</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/fullstory-collaboration-culture-with-google-workspace-and-gemini</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Beyond the prompt: How to create a Google Guides program to drive adoption of Workspace with Gemini</title>
        <description>The Google Guides Program is designed to drive the adoption of Google Workspace with Gemini by equipping users with the knowledge and skills to move &apos;beyond the prompt.&apos; This initiative provides practical guidance, training, and best practices for leveraging AI across applications like Gmail and Docs, helping users maximize productivity and creativity while addressing potential challenges.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/beyond-prompt-google-guides-program-to-drive-adoption-workspace-gemini</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/beyond-prompt-google-guides-program-to-drive-adoption-workspace-gemini</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Bringing human ingenuity and gen AI into creative harmony</title>
        <description>MAS, a global apparel and textile manufacturer, is augmenting human ingenuity with generative AI within Google Workspace, significantly enhancing its design and operational processes. By using AI tools like Gemini to accelerate ideation, optimize workflows, and analyze complex data, MAS reduces time-to-market and fosters innovation across its creative teams, demonstrating the power of human-AI collaboration.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 19:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/mas-human-ingenuity-with-gen-ai</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/mas-human-ingenuity-with-gen-ai</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Start a conversation with Gemini in the side panel of Google Drive about specific files</title>
        <description>Google Drive now allows users to start conversations with Gemini directly about specific files like Docs, Sheets, Slides, and PDFs, leveraging the file&apos;s content for context. Gemini can summarize documents, answer questions, and provide insights, enhancing productivity and understanding of file contents. This feature is available to Workspace users with Gemini Business, Enterprise, or Education upgrades, and Gemini Advanced subscribers, with a gradual rollout from May 2, 2025.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/start-conversation-with-gemini-in-drive-about-specific-files.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/05/start-conversation-with-gemini-in-drive-about-specific-files.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google named a leader in IDC Marketscape: Worldwide Team Collaboration Applications 2024 Vendor Assessment</title>
        <description>Google Workspace has been named a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Team Collaboration Applications 2024 Vendor Assessment, recognizing its robust suite of tools for enhancing teamwork and productivity. This acknowledgment highlights Google Workspace&apos;s strengths in integrating AI, fostering seamless communication, and supporting diverse organizational needs for effective collaboration.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/google-named-leader-idc-marketscape-worldwide-team-collaboration-applications</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/google-named-leader-idc-marketscape-worldwide-team-collaboration-applications</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Enhance Your Organization’s Security with Out-of-Domain File Warnings in Google Workspace</title>
        <description>Google Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides are introducing new out-of-domain file warnings to enhance data security for Google Workspace users. These warnings will alert users when they open files originating from outside their organization&apos;s trusted domain, helping to prevent accidental data leakage. This feature, gradually rolling out from April 24, 2025, is particularly beneficial for users leveraging Advanced Protection Program or strict Workspace security settings.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/out-of-domain-file-warnings-for-drive-docs-sheets-slides-files.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/out-of-domain-file-warnings-for-drive-docs-sheets-slides-files.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace Updates Weekly Recap - April 25, 2025</title>
        <description>The Google Workspace release notes for April 25, 2025, announced several updates, including the expansion of NotebookLM&apos;s Audio Overviews to 35 new languages and the introduction of out-of-domain file warnings in Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides for enhanced security. Additionally, Google Vids is now available for Business Starter, Enterprise Starter, and Nonprofits editions, while Gmail users can enjoy new emoji reactions.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Vids</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/release-notes-04-25-2025.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/04/release-notes-04-25-2025.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>New AI capabilities in Workspace to help every business drive results</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is rolling out new AI features, primarily through Gemini, designed to drive tangible business results by boosting productivity and fostering innovation. These AI capabilities help automate tasks such as content drafting, data analysis, and summarizing information, enabling businesses to make faster decisions and improve efficiency across their operations, from small businesses to large enterprises.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 15:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/new-ai-drives-business-results</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/new-ai-drives-business-results</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>March Workspace feature drop: More effective meetings, AI features for Vids, and more language capabilities</title>
        <description>The March Google Workspace feature drop brings new AI capabilities and enhancements across various applications, significantly boosting productivity and collaboration. Key updates include smarter drafting in Gmail, improved data analysis in Google Sheets, and advanced content generation with Gemini, designed to streamline workflows and foster creativity for users.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/march-workspace-feature-drop</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/march-workspace-feature-drop</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>5 ways to help your small business thrive with Google Drive</title>
        <description>Google Drive offers five essential ways to help small businesses thrive, focusing on secure collaboration, efficient file management, and robust data backup. These include easy sharing, version control, offline access, integration with Google Workspace apps, and reliable cloud storage, empowering small businesses to improve productivity and ensure business continuity.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 19:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/five-ways-help-your-small-business-thrive-google-drive</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/productivity-collaboration/five-ways-help-your-small-business-thrive-google-drive</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>See summaries of shared Google Docs, Slides, or Sheets files directly in Google Chat</title>
        <description>Google Chat will now automatically generate summaries of shared Google Workspace files, including Docs, Sheets, Slides, and PDFs, when they are linked in a chat conversation. This AI-powered feature enables users to quickly grasp the essence of a document without leaving Google Chat, significantly improving workflow efficiency. The feature is available for Google Workspace Business, Enterprise, Education Plus, and Teaching and Learning Upgrade customers.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Chat</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/summaries-of-shared-workspace-files-in-google-chat.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/summaries-of-shared-workspace-files-in-google-chat.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The future of work is here: Top Workspace sessions you don’t want to miss at Cloud Next ’25</title>
        <description>Google Cloud Next &apos;25 highlighted top Google Workspace sessions focused on transforming work with AI, featuring deep dives into Gemini&apos;s capabilities and practical applications. Sessions covered topics like enhancing productivity in Google Docs and Sheets, improving collaboration with AI-powered features, and ensuring enterprise-grade security and compliance within the Workspace ecosystem.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Cloud</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/top-workspace-sessions-at-cloud-next-25</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/top-workspace-sessions-at-cloud-next-25</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Use Gemini in the side panel of Workspace apps in four more languages</title>
        <description>The Gemini side panel, integrated across various Google Workspace applications such as Docs, Sheets, and Slides, is expanding its language support to include four additional languages. This enhancement makes AI assistance more accessible and useful for a wider global audience of non-English speaking users. This continuous language expansion improves the overall user experience and productivity within Workspace.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/four-additional-languages-supported-in-gemini-side-panel.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2025/03/four-additional-languages-supported-in-gemini-side-panel.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace with Gemini: 128 ways our customers are transforming how they work with AI</title>
        <description>Google Workspace customers like ATB Financial, Equifax, and Augustana University are transforming their work with AI, leveraging Gemini to enhance productivity and innovation. These organizations use AI to automate routine tasks, streamline content creation in Docs and Gmail, accelerate data analysis in Sheets, and foster deeper collaboration, demonstrating significant operational efficiencies and business value across diverse industries.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 21:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/how-our-customers-transform-work-with-ai</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/how-our-customers-transform-work-with-ai</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Forum Virium Helsinki builds a thriving workplace with Google Workspace and Gemini</title>
        <description>Forum Virium Helsinki, a municipal innovation company, is building a thriving workplace by leveraging Google Workspace to enhance collaboration and operational efficiency. The suite of tools, including Google Docs, Sheets, and Meet, enables their project-based teams to communicate seamlessly, manage projects effectively, and foster an innovative environment focused on developing smart city solutions for Helsinki.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Meet</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/forum-virium-helsinki-builds-thriving-workplace</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/forum-virium-helsinki-builds-thriving-workplace</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>How gen AI can help us make better decisions</title>
        <description>Generative AI, particularly tools like Gemini within Google Workspace, can help us make better decisions by rapidly synthesizing vast amounts of information, identifying patterns, and simulating various scenarios. By automating data analysis in Google Sheets and generating comprehensive reports in Google Docs, AI empowers decision-makers with deeper insights and reduces cognitive load, leading to more informed and strategic outcomes.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>NotebookLM</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 20:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/how-gen-ai-can-help-us-make-better-decisions</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/how-gen-ai-can-help-us-make-better-decisions</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Uber resolves issues faster with Google AppSheet and Google Apps Script</title>
        <description>Uber is resolving issues faster by leveraging Google AppSheet and Google Apps Script to create custom applications that streamline internal operations and enhance productivity for its global workforce. These no-code and low-code solutions automate complex workflows, integrate with Google Workspace data sources like Google Sheets, and reduce manual intervention, improving efficiency across various departments.</description>
		
		<tools>AppSheet</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Apps Script</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Drive</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/uber-resolves-issues-faster-google-appsheet-and-google-apps-script</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/customer-stories/uber-resolves-issues-faster-google-appsheet-and-google-apps-script</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Google Workspace enables the future of AI-powered work for every business</title>
        <description>Google Workspace is empowering businesses with new AI capabilities, primarily through Gemini, designed to enhance productivity, streamline operations, and foster innovation across all sizes of organizations. These AI features are integrated into core applications like Gmail, Docs, and Sheets, enabling users to automate routine tasks, generate high-quality content, and gain deeper insights from their data.</description>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/empowering-businesses-with-ai</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/product-announcements/empowering-businesses-with-ai</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>4 ways Gemini for Workspace can help sellers and marketers spend more time doing what they do best</title>
        <description>Gemini in Google Workspace offers four key ways to help sellers and marketers focus on their core competencies: automating content creation for emails and presentations, summarizing market research, analyzing sales data, and personalizing customer communications. This AI integration allows them to streamline routine tasks, enhance outreach strategies, and gain deeper insights, ultimately boosting productivity and customer engagement.</description>
		
		<tools>Gemini</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Workspace</tools>
		
		<tools>Gmail</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Docs</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Sheets</tools>
		
		<tools>Google Slides</tools>
		
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/4-ways-gemini-workspace-can-help-sellers-and-marketers-spend-more-time-doing-what-they-do-best</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://workspace.google.com/blog/ai-and-machine-learning/4-ways-gemini-workspace-can-help-sellers-and-marketers-spend-more-time-doing-what-they-do-best</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>